hi guys
so today is sunday 30th of may hope you
are having a nice weekend
uh first and foremost thank you to some
more subscribers
and taking the view count almost close
to 8 000
so thank you very much for that if you
like the video
please do subscribe and uh let's move on
uh so in this video i will be speaking
about
icici lombard general insurance as
cara is straightforward it is general
insurance matlab
a screenplay website so car insurance
two-wheeler health
travel etc and life insurance of icici
from icici is icici prudential life
insurance
so incu that's how it is divided so
lombard gives the general insurance
and i would say is the biggest
competitor or one of the biggest
competitor
competitor is bajaj finserv but of
course this is also a very crowded
sector is my hdfc
sbi uh these are
larson and two bro be here i'm just
talking of some of the big names
plus there will always be lot of other
smaller
uh second tier companies as well so
let's
move forward this is a large cap company
with the market cap of 67th almost seven
market
for some capacity uh so it's it's with
grasim and
sbi life and it's i'm surprised why
it isn't diversified whereas i think
insurance with me companies like his sub
insurance companies
[Music]
so it's a fairly expensive stock if you
look at the average of the nifty or if
the
if you look at the average of nifty 500
etc
so what the products are manga stock
um now this is on the nse website
sector index is nifty financial services
sector pe 24 this makes more sense nifty
financial services
symbol pe i don't know why zero here but
like we saw before 45 kaiser p here is
almost double so yes it is a fairly
expensive uh
stock and company information financial
results
i say q4 profit rises 22
okay so positive uh result
yeah again 23 i will put the links you
can check out the articles later
but now the interesting part is just
look at the one month chart hardly four
percent up
which means
so in spite of having almost a 25 up
net profit which is the main thing in
the business the net profit
stock did not react
i was hoping it will close above 1500
psychological resistance but did not
happen
uh stock went all the way up till 1567
if i'm not mistaken what love casino
1567 baby
bike uh 52 week high 1626 so not very
far away almost
just about eight percent away
approximately
so but is 1500
1500 coffee bar but
then ended the day at 14 90. so monday
will be extremely crucial
to see if this fellow can either stay
above 1500 or again back to
back to its major supports which is
about 1350 levels
1500 is
and then back down to 1450 and now again
going up
so what straightforward range high which
is about
1350 to 1500 ucomra and this was my last
trade
and i will of course share with you what
my thoughts are on this but first let's
more importantly see what the analysts
have to say
share khan target is 1750 so as you know
the 52 week high is 16 26
so this is 1750 with the 52 week high
say we about 7 8
on top good to know uh
capital via global target 1590 so say
sola so approximately
uh i see i say i see ici securities
you haven't given up sister company
because they have uh given a target
price
again you can say 1600 approximately not
too many analysts are covering this
uh stock and even access direct usually
joint summary that
i have so even that is not available so
you can see that it is not
a very uh not covered by many analysts
and
one point which i forgot let's going
back here if you look at the one year
chart
stock hardly pandra percent of it and
say my name is
so in a time when nifty has so this
stock has underperformed the nifty
plus if you look at one year mandara
percent we are at a time when
uh x almeid companies across sectors
have given 200 percent 150 percent on
the
unreal returns
but that is how it is it's still
nonetheless a blue chip company
but with little less volume and little
less price movement
uh so if someone is not invested in the
stock or has never dealt with it before
keep this in view
but as you can see from the chart this
will not give you
too many bumper returns nor will it
crash in a bumper way
compared to many other stocks option
chain
is very very interesting
1 lakh 62 000 open
that the option traders are expecting
but next major target is 1600 so this
option chain
is very positive from my perspective
this is my holding like i said my last
trade was 1350 to 1500
now i have made a kind of a clock major
investment
at about 15 22 is
so my cost would be about 1500
approximately
and my target would be 1600 share khan
target of 1750 i would be very happy if
it gets there
at this moment it's too early to say
i will stick with sixteen hundred as my
target where i will
liquidate at least part and book some
profits and other stock
or bhagra then of course uh uh it would
be in
uncharted territory and then i will just
take share khan 1750
as my next target so yeah that's it for
now guys
please do like the video if you like the
content and please do subscribe if you
have not
so thank you for watching and have a
great weekend bye